{
    "subject": "Demi_Moore",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ashton_Kutcher",
    "human_readable": "Demi Moore is married to Ashton Kutcher.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988497793674469,
            "question": "Is Ashton Kutcher married to Demi Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9868484139442444,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Demi Moore and Ashton Kutcher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9495100378990173,
            "question": "Are Demi Moore and Ashton Kutcher a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.909785270690918,
            "question": "To whom is Ashton Kutcher married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9031349420547485,
            "question": "Who are Ashton Kutcher and Demi Moore in a relationship with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8631686568260193,
            "question": "Who is Demi Moore married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7869982719421387,
            "question": "Name the husband of Demi Moore."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756109893321991,
            "question": "Who is Demi Moore's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.628542423248291,
            "question": "What is the name of Demi Moore's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5974708795547485,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Demi Moore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Demi Moore is married to Ashton Kutcher.",
            "html": "yago_28849_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Demi Moore's husband?",
            "html": "yago_28849_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Demi Moore's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28849_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the husband of Demi Moore.",
            "html": "yago_28849_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28849_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe text states that Demi Moore ended her marriage to Ashton Kutcher.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Demi Moore is married to Ashton Kutcher\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there are multiple documents mentioning Demi Moore and Ashton Kutcher, none of them explicitly state that they were married. However, some documents do mention their marriage in the past tense (e.g., \"her six-year marriage to Ashton\"), implying that their marriage has ended, but not confirming it was ever started."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Demi Moore and Ashton Kutcher were married, but they also indicate that Moore ended her marriage to Kutcher. Therefore, the statement \"Demi Moore is married to Ashton Kutcher\" is incorrect based on the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several news articles state that Demi Moore has decided to end her marriage to Ashton Kutcher.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the information from multiple sources (2, 4) indicates that Demi Moore was married to Ashton Kutcher in September 2005, but the information from sources (1 and 3) states that they got divorced after a six-year marriage, which suggests that the marriage occurred before their reported divorce.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Demi Moore has explicitly stated she is ending her marriage to Ashton Kutcher with the Associated Press, indicating they are no longer married.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}